Ok, ok, ok
Ok
It's about time
7.8
Ok, let's get started
Ok, let's have Juefei introduce himself
Ok, hello everyone, my name is Juefei He
I am a freelancer
I mainly do character modeling
That's about it
Ok, ok
We are very happy to invite Juefei to the BBB official live broadcast room
To do a special version of AMD learning
The first part will be Juefei to demonstrate
How to use various 3D software to complete his work
Ok, let's get started
Ok, the work this time is a down jacket
It looks like this
The work is basically done in AMD
And then
Well, this model is mainly
Let's start with the character model
This is the basic body of the character
The basic body of the character
And then
Here I have the basic body
I am from this
What is this called
It's from the dance studio
This is the dance studio
Because it will provide a lot of
Very useful
Very useful basic models
And then it's more convenient for you to pose
You have to adjust some of the characters
For example
Like this
Body shape
This kind of thing
I think it's more convenient
This live room will be harmonized
Ha ha ha
I don't think so
I see
Ha ha ha
It doesn't matter
The back is more suspicious than the front
Ha ha ha
OK, I'll change it
Change one
Yes, anyway, the basic body model of the character
I just
From this
It's made up in this
And then
The following is to enter MD
For example, you have chosen a model
Then choose
You have to do a pose
Then you can pour into your MD
Well, let me show you
My Maya
This one
Well
OK
I'm going in like this
And then I'm going to make an animation
Make an animation
Well
It's in MD
It will automatically make an animation
Oh no
In that stage
It will automatically make an animation
And then
In order to
At the beginning
When making the model
You must need an A pose
Or T pose
And then
Then
I need it to have a transformation
And then
It becomes the pose we want
In the middle of this
Let's do this
An explanation of the material
Well
And then
At the very beginning
That
The model in MD
It's actually like this
Oh
A basic
A pose
Well
And then
Now
The main problem
I guess a lot of friends
He may
Well
There may be some problems with the board
In fact
I make my own clothes
The board
It's not that
Go
On purpose
Find some
This
Very
Like a tailor-made
This kind of board shape
I mainly
Just with my
This reference picture
Let me show you the reference picture
The main thing is to cooperate with some of the reference pictures I found
Then
To carry out
The design and production of the board
Well
For example
Like this
U-shaped suit
Ah
Just a hat
Then
Add a jacket
Then there are some details here
Then
The main reference
May be this one
Well
Including some of the shoulders here
Some of the shapes
And this
The shape of the hat
Yes
Then
These reference pictures
Well
In fact
There are quite a lot of places to find
Like
I usually
I will go to Taobao
Find on me
Because there are a lot of clothes on Taobao
The shape is also very good
Especially those with relatively high sales
Then there are some
It may be through
I
Go online
Search
All kinds of collection
Well
I usually
When using MD
I often
Go online
Search some
That
Uh
References
Yes
I also used that
Then
If I take this hat
I will talk about the deck
Because I want to
Like clothes
Is actually
Just use
This is what we have here
Just use this MD
One of his
The shape of the clothes
Is also made from scratch
It's also very useful
Uh
What about most of my clothes
Is the part of clothing
Ah
All will be used
Like this
Uh
Basic form
Then
Like the hat
In fact
Maybe it's just a little bit more complicated
How do I deal with things like this?
I usually do it like this
I will build a
Let me hide all of this first
I will build a cap model like this
For example, like this
I will just drag it
For example, the shape here
I will just make a cap model like this
And then I will move it out
And then I will use something to divide the UV
This software is called RISMO
It used to be called RISMO
It's also a very useful UV thing
And then I will import it into this
And then I'll do a UV analysis
I'll guess
That's where we cut the UV
Where the UV is cut
We need it to do a cut
We need it to cut
It just needs a seam
We'll just cut it
I cut it casually
Like this
Actually this thing
This piece
Actually is the version I want
For example, my UV line
And then it's mixed with this line
So I can put this picture into this MD
And then I'm going to add a background image to the MD
And then I'm going to add it in
And then I'm going to use this tool
Oh, I'll use this
I'll use this
I'm going to use this tool after I get in
For example, I'm going to take this hat and I'm going to open it and I'm going to take a look at it
And then you get this one in this way
Um, it's a board
But maybe it's not the right size when you get it out
You can do it at that time
You can adjust it according to the specific model of this character
Right?
Um, that's when you don't know how to play board games
You can use this method
This is the first way
I'm just me
Um, it's not common
Anyway, it's the first way
And then the second way
MD has a very good function of its own
It's a flower line, right?
Because the biggest problem with playing board games is that it's not soundproof
Right?
If it's not soundproof
Because of everyone's figure
For example, if you choose a model figure
Well, it's not the same
So maybe I just want it to be a little bit more soundproof
For example, this pants
well
Maybe you just need to use this feature
Put it in here
I'm going to draw the whole thing
Right?
Draw it out
And you can connect this to this point
And then you can extract one of his panels in this way
You can use it to draw
In fact, we usually use MDGs
It's this kind of
Because to be honest, even if I'm a fashion expert, I can't even style my own clothes.
I just search online for something like pants styling.
And then I use it in MD.
Yes, that's basically how I use the template.
And then maybe in the later stages, I'll make some modifications to it.
It looks more horizontal and vertical.
And then...
For example, this is the first version.
Let's take a look at this line.
Now this one.
This one.
These are the points of the curve.
You can take a closer look at it.
It's based on the actual model you need.
To do this.
You can adjust it.
And then...
When I made this MD template,
I tried not to cut it too thin at the beginning.
You can make this template a little bit more complete.
Like here.
Where you don't need to cut, we'll try to...
Actually, you don't need to cut it.
Actually, these two should be two pieces.
But if I don't need to give different materials,
I don't need to cut it.
Because if you cut it too thin at the beginning,
it will take a lot of effort to adjust it later.
Including the sleeves here.
At the beginning, it's a...
Right?
At the beginning, it's a model like this.
It's the last one.
It's the last one you have to make.
And then you're almost done with this part.
You can cut this thing open and deal with it.
No problem.
Just don't cut it too thin at the beginning.
And then the board.
That's about it.
And then the rest.
Maybe it's because I like to do this kind of detail in this MD.
Including these little creases.
Including these sewing lines.
Including this kind of...
The thickness of this kind of stack of fabric.
I like to do it in MD.
The effect made in MD is also very good.
So...
So I'll...
Basically, I do things.
90%.
I don't need to change it when it comes out in MD.
It's just that I'm more satisfied with it.
Then you're still good at it.
You're better than me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
I just...
Because it's very well calculated.
And then I like to turn the lens very high.
Turn it up to two centimeters or something like that.
And then in the process of using it, I found that the effect was really good.
And then I...
No. 2, your computer doesn't lag.
Oh...
Okay.
I'm a little bit demanding about computers.
May be the computer should be a little better.
I'm so touched.
Someone asked me in the group before.
When the particle diameter was 10 mm.
He said it was very laggy.
Asked me how to do it.
I thought at the time,
I won't be lagging when I change the computer.
Yeah, I can say that.
No, no, no, no.
Actually, the particle diameter is 2mm.
This is not to say that.
That is,
I will need to change the shape of it in the case of 2mm or 5mm.
Most of the time, I still need to change its shape in the case of 10 or more.
I won't be able to fix it in the case of 2mm or 5mm.
Basically, for example, I will reduce the diameter of this large shape.
Let's make it 15.
Then, it will take a long time to wait.
It's okay.
Okay.
This is not a pair of pants. This is a model that I imported.
This is only the clothes. If I import the pants, I won't be able to fix it.
At the beginning, I will use this.
There are two sets of flowcharts.
I usually use two sets of flowcharts here.
One is the pure CPU calculation flowchart.
The other is the flowchart of the GPU.
This set of flowcharts is the flowchart of the CPU.
This is the flowchart of the CPU.
If I want to fix it, I should use the GPU.
Let me talk about GPU first.
This is my own production habit.
When I use GPU calculation,
the advantage of GPU calculation is that it can be dragged very smoothly.
Right? Very smoothly.
Then you adjust the shape, adjust the width, and the scale.
It's very convenient when you want to see something.
If you are not a good person, you may have some problems when calculating these small things.
But this is not a big problem.
If you say that Li Zhu's clothing will have a lot of layers.
For example, you have one layer and I have one layer.
For example, I take this one.
For example, my clothes.
It will have some layers.
What's going on?
How can this be used?
I understand.
For example, this will have some layers of this kind of blockage.
For example, this is inside this, right?
Then this is below this.
Then this belt is on top of this jack.
Then this cloak is on top of everything.
This layer is very rich.
But if you just want to process it in an AMD file,
I usually use CPU.
Then if this layer is not very rich,
there are some small things like this.
I usually use a process of GPU.
Then it will be faster to do this.
Then I will do it slowly.
I will improve the accuracy while doing it.
Usually it is 15.
Then turn on 10.
Then turn on 6.
Then turn on 8.
Then turn on 5.
Then it will be like this.
Then the final calculation.
In the final calculation, I will still use a CPU calculation.
Because the results of CPU and GPU are relatively high here.
There will be some very small differences.
Then I feel that the CPU results will be better.
Then I will calculate it at the end.
For example, if I calculate it to 5.
Then I will switch to CPU and let it calculate more accurately.
Yes.
In fact, when we usually use it,
we use a GPU.
It's all like this.
Yes, in the process of roughly before.
Then it will be changed to a CPU and then calculate again.
Yes.
This is the best effect.
Wait a minute.
Let me read the file again.
OK.
When I saw your competition work before,
I really like it.
Just for everyone.
This is the competition work I saw on the screen.
I felt that my last live broadcast was a waste of time.
Because I saw your competition work.
Then I took it out and compared it with mine.
I feel like I'm going to the amateur team.
Fortunately, I didn't participate in the competition.
No, I will spend more time.
I think there is a lot of time.
Then I calculate a little bit every day.
Probably it will take a long time.
Maybe it will be a little more complicated.
In fact, I don't think there is much difference between these contents, to be honest.
I think it looks very cool.
At first glance, it looks very cool.
I feel like I did it with all my heart.
Thank you.
Business is mutual.
You are right.
Then I will share some more about this MT production.
These are some of my own details.
For example, Like this one.
Here is.
Let me select the face.
Why forgot to hide it?
For example, like this kind of releasing thread.
I will use this kind of continuous smoke thread.
And then we will use another one,ашаfe-like.
To simulate a feeling of overlapping's arrive.
For example, this kind of fabric-divided detail.
I will use this kind of small production method
at the edge, including this kind of seam allowance,
to highlight the details of the two fabrics.
Then there is another one.
I will use some...
Here is also a fold.
There will be a fold inside.
Then it will probably give a feeling of bending inwards.
Then it will add a little bit of its elasticity.
Then there will be some very small details in this place.
I like to do some things like this.
Then there are also some folds on the surface.
How to lock it?
Wait a moment.
Okay.
For the details on the surface,
I may use a double layer.
For the bottom layer of the double layer,
I will...
This is the bottom layer.
Its stretch fineness is 100%.
Then the high layer will be slightly higher.
In this way,
if the stretch of the upper layer and the bottom layer
are different in the fineness,
we can see that there will be some folds
that are different from the fabric inside.
But this is one method.
This is just one method of production.
There is another method.
For example,
if you use this pin,
you can put...
This is a good card.
Yes.
When you look at the pin,
it's a little bit of a card.
Yes.
This is a little bit of a card.
There is another method.
You can put this circle around.
For example,
you choose the shape you want.
Then pin your circle.
Then we increase the fineness.
This is also a method.
These two methods can get the same effect.
I think.
But my personal opinion is that
I still prefer to use double layers.
Because double layers
will sew up all the lines inside.
In this way,
it will look better on the edge of this envelope.
There will be a shape like this here.
It's bulging.
Then thread it in.
Then a shape comes out like this.
Because it will sew up these two lines.
This seam line
is sewn up with the seam line above you.
I personally prefer to do this.
Then,
let me see.
What else is there?
I think...
It's stuck.
After you finish talking,
I guess a lot of things will jump out of my section.
Because I've already talked about it here.
It's okay.
The application is different.
everyone
theby
The application is different.
The way ofıyoruz
You can draw the pattern whenever you like.
In does not change the style of your artwork.
The таких
DD
It has to make the pattern
It's first time,
Select the sewing line and then make some sewing lines, and then this sewing line can actually be done
Uh, some very fancy things, for example, you're up there
For example, you draw a good-looking one
For example, some pattern shapes, these things, right
Pattern shapes and then you can use this sewing line and then you can import a model like this that you want
Uh, a model of a braid
A model of a braid is a model of a braid, which means you can make some pattern shapes very quickly in here
It's not necessarily a sewing line. If it's a sewing line, sometimes I'll do it that way
well
And then I'll see what else there is
How do you fix the tie on the leg of a large pattern
There's a serious deformation
It's down here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in here and you're in
No, I used to sit separately, but now I don't sit together because it's too laggy and I can't eat well.
The legs are not very well made.
This part is similar to this part.
First of all, I will make it a little tighter.
For the legs, I will give a material separately.
For this material, I will increase the friction between the fabrics.
This is a good way to create friction with the fabric.
Secondly, when you get a good result, you freeze it and it won't slide down.
Then you just need to adjust the inside.
Sometimes I will increase the friction inside.
I will make it a little smaller.
Then I won't make this part difficult.
I will do this for the legs.
Sometimes it's hard to slide down.
The main reason is that the board is too small or too tight.
Just like people wear socks.
If your socks are tight, your socks will roll down.
The bag on the MD is too tight.
I usually put it in the freezer.
Because I don't want to make it too big.
You can adjust the size of the bag.
Yes, if you want to adjust it after you've done it,
it will be a bit hard, to be honest.
There is one more thing I forgot to mention.
The model itself,
I usually adjust its friction coefficient.
At the beginning, it might be 0.5,
and at the end it might be 0.85,
or whatever the friction coefficient is.
If you adjust it higher,
you can create more wrinkles
if you don't adjust it higher.
Otherwise, it will slide down all at once.
This makes it more uncomfortable.
Yes.
Other than that,
I don't think there is anything else.
How about we move on to the next part?
To the next process.
Let's move on to the next step.
Okay.
I thought you were going to ask me
if I could make it faster.
I was like, what?
It's so fast.
No, no, no.
I'm not ready yet.
In the end,
when you are satisfied with the result,
I will select the surface.
After selecting it,
I will create two models.
Let me show you.
Here.
Actually, I wanted to add a bag to it,
and glasses.
Then I thought,
never mind.
Let me see where it is.
Which one is it?
Hmm.
This is the model I made at the time.
The one for the board.
Actually, you can see
there is a big difference
between this model and the final model.
Hmm.
There is a big difference between this model and the final model.
Actually, this is just a reference.
In the end,
you still need to modify it
according to your reference picture or beauty.
Let me see where it is.
Here.
Okay.
Then,
here,
I will make a set.
Hmm.
Let me see where it is.
This is the modified version.
Hmm.
Yes.
Anyway, that's it.
I will make a set.
This is the modified version.
Then there is another set.
Hmm.
There is another set.
This is the set of clothes inside.
I will make two sets.
First,
I will take it out to the Zbrush.
Let me take it out.
Let me take it out to the Zbrush and try it.
Hmm.
When I take it out,
I made a triangle face.
It is still a triangle face.
That is,
I won't take out the four sides.
Because the four sides,
first of all,
this is relatively high.
Then,
it will take a lot of time
when it is converted.
So I will make a triangle face.
Hmm.
Go to ZB.
When it comes to ZB, it looks like this.
Let's pretend that it's a triangle.
Pretend that it's a triangle.
Because it takes too long to reset.
Let's do a zero mesh for it.
Zero mesh.
A few days ago, a friend of mine asked me if I could add a zero mesh to my MD.
I said, okay, okay, okay.
I'm going to ask for a function development request.
And then I really wrote it down.
I haven't read the feedback yet.
If it works well in the MD, I don't think there's going to be any trouble like me.
It's definitely going to be more convenient.
And then after it's done, I'll call it back.
I took it.
w w w here.
Oh, oh, it's in.
And then, okay.
And then it's here.
If it's a zero mesh, it's going to have some problems.
There are some places where it's going to be like this.
You can see that it can't be connected.
And then all of this stuff, all of these problems, all of these problems,
We need to deal with it manually.
Just like this.
For example, just add a dot.
And then I'm going to put it up here.
There's a little line here.
There's a face here.
Okay.
Just like this.
These places where there's a problem.
All of this is going to be dealt with.
That's it.
Right?
All of this is going to be dealt with one by one.
Including these curves.
These things.
That's why I didn't like to cut this board too much in the beginning.
It's because the repair process behind it is too huge.
If I cut it too much.
I've been fixing it for too long.
So sometimes I can put it together.
I put it together.
And if you put it together like this, the effect will be better if you put it together.
Okay.
And then.
And then we'll see.
For example, the number of faces of my model.
And then I'm going to make a face for the whole model.
For example, the model I made.
The model I made.
Three-sided.
It's 18 million faces.
Right?
18 million faces.
And then I'm going to match it here.
It's basically a model I've fixed.
It's probably as high as this.
It's not as high as I said just now.
This is a model I made.
And it's a model that I've manually fixed.
The number of faces of this model is 200,000.
Basically 200,000.
100,000.
X 16.
It's a little bit more than that.
Almost.
That's what I finally need.
A face of a model.
That's what I.
How to say.
It's equivalent to.
It's equivalent to a split of two times.
It's equivalent to a split of two levels.
Am I still here?
I'm here.
Split of two levels.
That's as much as you can.
Your final result.
The accuracy of this face model.
That's the number of faces.
Don't be lower than this.
That's the number of faces you've calculated.
Don't be lower than this number of faces.
Right?
And then here.
I'm going to use a method.
Because we didn't.
It's already.
For example, I'm going to draw this three-sided face.
Okay.
For example, let's assume this is the model I've made.
It's stuck.
Let's say, for example, this is a model we've made.
And then we have one.
It's a model we've made through this mesh.
We only have two models.
Now we need to.
It's going to be a transfer.
And then.
And then I'm stuck now.
I was thinking.
Why isn't my screen moving?
What's covering my eyes?
No, no.
I moved that.
I moved his whole face.
And then Maya.
If you move his face, he'll be stuck.
Let's take a look again.
This.
There's a comment.
What's the reason for the transfer to Maya?
Is it for the line?
Yes, it's for the line.
Because.
From MD.
I'll show you this MD.
That's it.
Actually, you don't have to use a needle.
You can show it directly on the left.
But it doesn't matter.
I'm afraid of the left side.
I'm afraid it's too stuck.
All right.
Because MD.
It's like this.
It may not be suitable for us to make further corrections and carvings.
Because it's all triangular.
And then.
And then after we.
A process like ZB.
You can make sure it's basically a four-sided surface.
And then after the four-sided surface is divided.
After we print it back to Maya.
After printing back to this original dress.
It's more convenient for us.
It's a follow-up carving.
For example.
This is what I've redone.
It's a good face.
Right.
And then I'm going to hide all this stuff.
So much.
And then this is what we got out of MD.
Right.
And then we're going to use one of these.
A function to transmit attributes.
For example.
I need this.
This one.
My own.
The UV information of this mask.
To be transmitted.
Wait a minute.
I'll delete the UV.
Okay.
For example.
This is a mask that we made.
Right.
And then this is our original.
Maya.
This is the mask in MD.
And then I need to put this.
Mask in Maya.
No.
The mask in MD.
And then.
To the side of the mask.
Right.
Then I choose to transmit.
This.
We'll choose Copy.
Select UV.
Select World OTA.
Click passing.
OK.
It's hereditary.
So these two masks need to have the same UV.
Then I didn't pass on.
Overwatch.
First choose MD, captured and then your other makeshift mask.
And then I chose to pass.
OK.
I want to have one.
What?
No problem.
I chose the wrong one.
There's another one in there.
I said, what's going on?
Okay.
So I have two sets of the same UV,
but different layers.
Now I need
to put this
one that you don't want to have
and then pass it to
the one you already have
in MD
on a fabric model.
You can see that the UV of this panel is the same.
There may be something missing. I don't remember.
And then the same
It seems
that the network is lagging.
Wait a minute.
Because I turned on the accelerator,
the network may be disconnected.
Hello?
Okay.
My accelerator
is disconnected.
It's okay.
It should be fine.
Okay. Let's continue.
Now we have two
same UVs,
but different layers.
Now I need to
put the model
of the four sides
that I have organized
and then pass it
to the model
of MD.
So I choose the model of MD first.
Then I choose
the one that I have processed.
And then the one above
is the attribute
that I want to pass.
I want to pass the vertex coordinates,
and then the following is the source of the transfer.
I can choose the source
and its UV.
Because in this case,
the UVs of the two models are the same.
Then I want to pass it first.
Well,
okay.
Then this
model that I have reorganized
will be very good
to pass to
the model of MD.
Then this line of line
of MD,
I think it's more suitable
for me
to do some further carving,
or some other adjustments.
That's it.
And then
here,
because
its progress is still
different.
This progress is still a little bit
lower.
Then I will do a detail for it
Anyway, I will do the same thing with the model I made in MD.
Then we will transfer these models directly to ZB.
Let's see.
I see that there is a live chat.
Can't I just send it directly to you?
About sending it directly,
I had a chat with my friends in QNU.
MD's current top is still based on the 2D version of Remeshing because of our remeshing.
So if you directly remesh to Redapology,
it's still not what you want.
I also mentioned the development of the function.
I hope it can be online soon.
Just like everyone usually uses ZE.
It's the same as ZB's remeshing.
Because MD's current remeshing is still...
Actually, I think MD's remeshing is still good.
I think it can be used.
But especially if my accuracy is very high,
for example, if my accuracy is 2,
basically my computer can't run.
That's the main problem.
But I think it's still good to use.
It's better than ZB's remeshing.
And it's more convenient.
Yes.
But actually,
I've also asked some game companies before.
The big guys in the game companies always reply to me like this.
They always say,
Can you make a simplified version of MD for me?
I don't want anything from top remeshing and UV editor.
I don't want any of them.
I can use other software to complete it.
Can't you make MD a little simpler?
Can't you do the material resolution?
At that time, I was like,
Let me make a simplified version of MD for a functional development demand.
And then I wrote it on the MD functional development demand.
Chen Xuanyuan still hasn't replied to my development demand.
Chen Xuanyuan, I worked so hard to write such a thing.
And then you tell me you don't want it?
Yes.
They may not want to talk to me at all.
Yes, I guess so.
Anyway, in the later process,
after I dive in,
I will,
because it's a whole.
You can see that I've already divided it into pieces here.
They're all divided into pieces.
And then how do I divide this?
I will separate the places that need thickness separately.
And then there is no need for thickness.
Sometimes you don't need to make a double layer.
And then you divide it into another piece like this.
Turn it off.
Then this piece,
this one at the back,
this thing at the back,
it should actually have thickness.
That is to say,
if there is no thickness,
it will look a little bit more fake.
And then I will deal with this thickness in this ZB.
And then there are some,
for example,
there will be a little bit of this kind of problem between the panels.
I may be able to manually adjust it for you.
Adjust it manually.
Yes.
And then the other words.
Let me see what else there is.
And then there is MD,
which is the model you import in.
It may not be as smooth as I am.
I'll give you one of them.
Come in and try it.
This is not right.
Is it my side?
This is a little bit of a problem with the model processing.
This one.
Which one is it?
Let's look for it.
ZB Mesh.
Why is it gone?
Close.
The chat says there are so few people today.
I think there may be some misunderstandings in the chat.
There are a lot of people today.
It's just that everyone is not posting chats.
But it may be.
Do you have it locked?
Then let me talk about the back first,
let it get stuck in this place.
Because there are too many faces.
And then there are some small components.
These things can be completely in Maya or ZB,
or you can use other softwares you want,
go in and make a production.
Then I carved a little bit in here.
These details are actually all calculated by MD.
I didn't do any carving.
Then the place I carved may only be here.
Here, just a little bit of it.
Maybe I will use a brush that I like.
For example, I should use this brush.
It's too heavy.
Because I don't have a digital tablet.
This kind of brush.
Then I will add some of these very small details.
Including here.
I will add these very small details.
These details are basically all calculated by MD.
I won't move it.
Then...
Including...
Where did I add it?
I may have changed the gloves a little bit.
Because MD is still a bit difficult to calculate gloves.
For me.
I may not be able to calculate it well.
Because I saw a lot of people on the Internet
who are very good at counting shoes and gloves.
I'm not good at it anyway.
I'll just do it.
I'll just do it normally.
Then I may go here.
To brush some details like this.
Brush some details like this.
Well, there's nothing else.
Just some regular modeling.
Some of the regular ones.
Like this kind of button modeling.
Button modeling.
It's very simple.
There's also a card line.
Let me see if it's good here.
It's good.
ZB.
This is just one model.
It's on the second floor.
It's too big.
This is what I did.
Through printing.
Then through.
It's just a series of operations.
Through printing.
Through turning.
Then through this kind of thing.
You can see it.
Because after all, it's your bottom.
It's the MD of printing.
The model solved by MD.
So more or less.
It's going to be a little bit.
It's this kind of uneven phenomenon.
The uneven phenomenon.
So I'm here.
And then it's this.
The number of faces.
It's only one million faces.
It's not in line with our high-end carving standards.
And then here.
I might turn off this smooth.
And then make a detail.
For example.
Just add a few points.
To avoid being too laggy.
And then do another.
It's called.
Mask.
Then mask its border.
And then I'm going to mask all of its edges.
And then I'm going to do a.
One.
Polish.
OK.
You can see this.
It's very smooth.
Right.
And then I'm going to remove the edge.
Yeah.
And then we're going to do this operation.
And then.
You can get.
We.
Well.
This.
The.
Back.
Such a model.
And then we divided it into pieces.
To handle.
To deal with.
Um.
That.
The high model is actually.
That's it.
High model.
I don't.
That is, to make a special.
Finishing.
Or to make a simplification.
Because.
When we make game models.
Especially for mobile games.
It's a little bit.
Some of the frills may need to be simplified in order to make it look more logical.
We may need to erase some of the frills to make it look more logical.
Since this is my own work, I won't be thinking about this.
Let's move on to the next step.
This is a demo of the model that I have already made.
You can see that I haven't made a demo yet.
This is the same as when we did the printout.
We used this as the minimum detail for the panel when we did the printout for the first time.
We will then make a copy of the height model in ZB.
I will make a separate group of the height model.
I will combine them into the ABCDEFG.
I will make a group of models and separate them.
And then, just like this, give it a material ball and then separate it.
And then in the high mode, you can see that my name is also ABCDEFG, right?
M-EF, M-H, this side is also LMEF, right?
And then the corresponding one here is also LME-6, right?
And then do a backup like this.
For UV, I will use this Arisma.
This is the software we just used.
Arisma, and then do a re-arrangement and processing.
This is horizontal and vertical.
And then I will make some adjustments to its orientation.
And then avoid that when we go up to the sun,
the orientation of the two objects is different.
These are some of the regular processes of making games.
Okay.
Then we will...
go to the last step.
The last step...
Oh, it's not the last step.
It's the second step.
Material.
Oh, then I will throw it into MD...
Oh, no.
Into SP.
Into SP to make materials.
And then this material I made is also very simple.
It's just that there are not so many scratches.
Or it's not enough.
These things.
It's very simple.
Just find it from there.
After you find it,
then drag it up.
Then try which one is more suitable.
Then I used more of this MD...
This SP's official material library.
I used more of it.
What's in it?
Laser.
And then Fabric.
Right?
I'll go in there and find it.
This material.
And then I'll drag it up when I find it.
Drag it up to see if the effect is OK.
That's it.
And then I'll just pour it out.
Right?
There are probably so many materials.
And then I might add some like this.
Some small hair lines on the surface.
Make it...
This kind of foundation will be a little stronger.
Like this.
This kind of hair line at the back.
I'll add a little bit.
Add a little bit.
These things are all in SP.
Go into production.
And then after it's done,
I'll show you this.
Well...
This one.
And then there are a few of these.
This material group.
Material group.
It's AptlyEFG.
Right?
This is a few sets of materials.
OK.
I'll give this one to...
Rebuild it.
Let's see how to rebuild it.
Rebuild it like this.
OK.
And then...
Well...
I'll open my eight boxes.
At the end,
I'll tell you a little bit about...
The rendering and lighting.
That's how I do it.
OpenSense.
The eight boxes.
This eight-box file is also very large.
I suggest that maybe...
Our computer is a little better.
This kind of...
Because I'm already a bit stuck here.
And I haven't turned on the effect yet.
Then I'll import it here.
And then...
Make a adjustment in SP.
And then I personally...
In the rendering eight boxes.
I prefer...
For these fabric materials.
Will also add some effects of 3S.
Because in this way,
It can soften our shadow.
Improve our rendering effect.
The other thing is...
Regular PBR cutout.
And then we'll put these...
The hair line.
Abito.
These things.
Pour it in.
Right?
And then there's one here.
Oops.
I'm stuck.
The structure.
And then I'll show you the effect.
If you turn on the effect.
The effect will be better.
But it will be stuck to death.
This is the effect after turning on the effect.
The effect in the eight boxes.
And then this is the effect after turning it off.
Right?
It's very obvious.
The effect will be much better after turning it on.
And then on the ground.
On the ground.
I just hope.
It's a real costume.
I just want to make it.
That is to say.
More realistic.
This ground.
In fact, it's very simple.
Just use our.
SA.
To make a production.
We just need to find one.
This.
In.
For example.
The ground.
It's in here.
Find the corresponding.
Your favorite.
The material ball on the ground.
And then stack another.
S.
O,
I.
Now.
We can change it.
One.
S.
1.
So.
Here.
he mean.
He is from chutney.
There.
Then at the bottom of the building.
He is what.
So.
The water works.
For the light in here, I usually look at everyone's type.
If you want to experience a more cool feeling,
I can take a look at the top light from the top light.
If you want to show the overall appearance of an object,
we will take a look at the light from the front.
And then the back three lights are all a outline light.
You can see this picture.
This is a picture of an outline light with a closed main light and a floating light.
We can add an outline light when we show it.
It will look better like this.
And then the main light and the floating light,
one is to create a shadow,
and the other is to correct its shadow.
Mainly these two functions.
There are not many lights.
Anyway, it's probably like this.
My main light should be this one.
Because this is the brightest one.
There is a back light from the back.
It's a light like this.
Then it will look more comfortable in the back light.
Then it will look more comfortable in the front light.
This is nothing to say.
Then it will look like this.
This is all I have now.
It's nothing.
It's over so quickly.
Yeah, that's all.
It's gone.
But it's still very handsome.
I remember when I first saw this picture,
I was thinking,
Ah, is this really the clothes that MD can make?
Really?
Yes, it is.
MD is still very strong.
I think his ability to calculate the speed is really the strongest.
It's the time of the business car.
Why don't I take a look at our question and answer session?
Wait a minute.
I'll start when I'm done.
I speak very fast.
Very fast.
Because there are a lot of parts you talked about.
I can jump over directly.
No, no, no.
I think it's really very marketable to make furniture.
Because now a lot of people actually make furniture in the industry.
It's all MD.
Yes, I used MD to make this thing.
I used to have a friend who played games with me.
Then I told him what he asked me to do.
I said I was doing fabric disassembly.
Then he said,
Ah, we have a very good fabric disassembly tool here.
Called Marvelous Designer.
Do you know?
And then I said I don't know to prevent technical support.
Is there such a good software?
He said yes.
It's really easy to use.
I said, okay, I'll go down now.
This is a little awkward.
This is also a real question.
Just ask this.
Or ask you directly.
Yes.
Then he said,